<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<dataset>
  <title>Assumptions and Stereotypes</title>
 

   <instruction>
    <desktop>To complete this activity, select each question and then click the matching suspect. To unmatch, select the matched suspect again. Replay this interaction as many times as you need. There is no time limit. Your responses will not be graded.</desktop>
    <mobile>To complete this activity, select each question and then click the matching suspect. To unmatch, select the matched suspect again. Replay this interaction as many times as you need. There is no time limit. Your responses will not be graded.</mobile>
  </instruction>
  <feedback>
  <correct>Correct! You've matched each question to the correct customer. You understand concepts related to assumptions and stereotypes.</correct>
  <wrong>Incorrect. Try again. Refer to Chapter 2 of your textbook to review assumptions and stereotypes.</wrong>
  </feedback>

  <items>
   <item>
      <clickable>
      <text><![CDATA[How does his appearance influence <br>this choice?]]></text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
      <text><![CDATA[Ja'Von Davis, Male, Age 15<br>Dressed in baggy jeans; cap pulled over his eyes; mumbled speech]]></text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
      <text><![CDATA[How do her emotions influence <br>this choice?]]> </text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
      <text><![CDATA[Allison Staumont, Female, Age 34<br>Accompanied by two toddlers; dressed in gym clothes; frazzled and harried]]></text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
      <text>How does his name influence this choice?</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
      <text><![CDATA[Enrique Chavez, Male, Age 57<br>Dressed in a business suit; grabs lunch; pumps gas]]></text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
      <text>How does her age influence this choice?</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>      
      <text><![CDATA[Julia Freeman, Female, Age 13<br>Dressed in jeans and an oversized sweatshirt; focused on smartphone as she stands in line]]></text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
      <text>How do his actions influence this choice?</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>      
      <text><![CDATA[Zach Atkinson, Male, Age 19<br>Wears a lanyard with a badge from a nearby community college; wanders around the store aimlessly]]></text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
      <text>How does her speech influence this choice?</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
      <text><![CDATA[Lucy Chu, Female, Age 23<br>Dressed in an anime T-shirt and tall black boots; smacks gum loudly; speaks sharply with an accent]]></text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    
    
  </items>
</dataset>