<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<dataset>
  <title>Media Types and Purposes</title>
 

   <instruction>
    <desktop>To complete the activity, select each term and then click the matching definition. To unmatch, select the matched definition again. Replay this interaction as many times as you need. There is no time limit. Your responses will not be graded.</desktop>
    <mobile>To complete the activity, select each term and then click the matching definition. To unmatch, select the matched definition again. Replay this interaction as many times as you need. There is no time limit. Your responses will not be graded.</mobile>
  </instruction>
  <feedback>
     <correct>Correct! You’ve matched each media type with its purpose. You understand that each media type serves a different purpose within a rhetorical situation.</correct>
     <wrong>Incorrect. Try again. Refer to the beginning of Chapter 18 of your textbook to review the media types and purposes you’re having trouble matching.</wrong>
  </feedback>

  <items>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Print Media (professional publications)</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>Highly respected; text-based; provides high level of credibility</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Advertisement</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>High cost; highly flexible; offers persuasive audiovisual messaging</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Radio/Podcast</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>Audio message; low cost; efficiently reaches a large number of people</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Website/ Blog/Vlog</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>      
        <text>Accessible for many users; incorporates visual, linguistic, and audio modes; reaches a wide audience</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Presentation</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>      
        <text>Incorporates text, images, and public speaking; often used to educate or inform</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Infographic</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>Primarily visual; combines facts with graphics; enhances an audience’s understanding of patterns and trends</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Photo Essay/Montage</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>      
        <text>Visual; powerfully conveys the emotion behind an issue, cause, or story</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>PSA</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>Combines audio and visual modes; persuades an audience; advocates for social change</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    
  </items>
</dataset>