<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<dataset>
  <title>Reasoning Strategies</title>
  <instruction>To complete the activity, select the claim at the top, then select the corresponding counterclaim below.  Replay this interaction as many times as you need. There is no time limit. Your responses will not be graded.</instruction>
  <rightfeedback>Correct! You’ve matched each scenario to the reasoning strategy it represents. You understand the different reasoning strategies and how they are used.</rightfeedback>
  <wrongfeedback>Incorrect. Try again. Refer to the beginning of Chapter 11 of your textbook to review the different reasoning strategies you may use as a writer.</wrongfeedback>
  <items>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Problem and Solution</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>To address the issue of employees taking sick days for personal business, the company allows a work-from-home day once per week.</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Analogy</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>You can best understand the many layers of media misinformation by thinking of an onion.</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Compare and Contrast</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>Like the old Antonio’s Pizzeria, the newer version has many menu items, but unlike the old Antonio’s, some of the favorites are not available.</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Cause and Effect</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>      
        <text>Because of flooding, roads were closed and traffic was rerouted throughout the city.</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Classification and Division</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>      
        <text>The company reorganization separated domestic and offshore interests.</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    <item>
      <clickable>
        <text>Definition</text>
      </clickable>
      <matching>
        <text>To accomplish detailed cake decorating, you’ll need a piping bag—a cone-shaped bag with a small hole at one end.</text>
      </matching>
    </item>
    

    
    
    
  </items>
</dataset>